(Amy:)Yeah, yeah, you want a cigarette.
Well, I'd like a normal boyfriend. Deal with it.
Oh. Hey, what's up?
(Penny:)Um...
(Penny:)You need me to shut the door
so you can do your knocking thing?
(Sheldon:)No. I didn't start yet. It's fine.
(Penny:)Okay. So, what do you need?
(Sheldon:)Well, I was thinking about
you helping me out last night.
(Sheldon:)Penny.
And I just wanted to tell you, Penny...
(Sheldon:)...that the answer to the question,
"Who did a great job?" is you.
(Sheldon:)Penny.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Sheldon:)You were very natural
in front of the camera...
(Sheldon:)...and I found your suggestions
extremely helpful.
Oh, sweetie, you just made my day.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Penny:)My acting class is putting on a play Friday.
I can put you and Amy on the guest list.